<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blog &#8211; House Of Roses</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/category/blog/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 16:19:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/cropped-cropped-Picture-768x742_web_icon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Blog &#8211; House Of Roses</title>
	<link>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Patience</title>
		<link>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/patience-2/</link>
					<comments>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/patience-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John Roseli]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 16:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://houseofroses.pnl.nyc/?p=274</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Patience ………………………………………… Patience …………………………………………………………… Patience. Having Patience can take quite a bit of patience. Patience may be one of the hardest hurdles to overcome when trying to become successful. But why be patient? You did all this work, you put in the time and you [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter"><img src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2018/02/14-Patience-291x300.jpg" alt="Patience" class="wp-image-257"/><figcaption>This image was not created by House of Roses. For concerns about this photo please contact: Mr.RosesEmail@gmail.com</figcaption></figure></div>



<p></p>



<p></p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Patience ………………………………………… Patience …………………………………………………………… Patience.</p>



<p>Having Patience can take quite a bit of patience. Patience may be one of the hardest hurdles to overcome when trying to become successful. But why be patient?</p>



<p>You did all this work, you put in the time and you made the sacrifices that you needed to make in order to achieve your goals. So why now do you now have to be patient to achieve success?</p>



<p>Well because not everything in life happens right away, for example consider farming. Farming is a labor demanding job. Farming has (6) basic steps that every farmer must make in order to grow plants, vegetables, fruits, exedra. These steps when broken down can act as a perfect simile to the patients needed to achieve your goals.</p>



<p><strong>1.) Crop Selection</strong>&nbsp;– Here the Farmer must decide on the seeds to plant.</p>



<p>* Here the successful person must decide on what type of goal they wish to accomplish.</p>



<p><strong>2.) Land Preparation</strong>&nbsp;– Here the Farmer must choose land and preparing it for the seeds.</p>



<p>* Here the successful person must begin laying down a plan for how to achieve their goals.</p>



<p><strong>3.) Seed Sowing</strong>&nbsp;– Here the Farmer must begin planting the seeds into the soil.</p>



<p>* Here the successful person must take action and start working according to their plan.</p>



<p><strong>4.) Irrigation</strong>&nbsp;– Here the Farmer must constantly water the crops to ensure their growth and development.</p>



<p>* Here the successful person must nurture the dream of their goal and continuously work on achieving it with faith in achieving the goal.</p>



<p><strong>5.) Crop Growth</strong>&nbsp;– Here the Farmer begins to see his crops rising from the soil.</p>



<p>* Here the successful person begins to see progress and results on their goals.</p>



<p><strong>6.) Harvesting</strong>&nbsp;– Here the Farmer begins to finally harvest fruits, vegetables, exedra from their crops.</p>



<p>* Here the successful person finally experiences results from their efforts.</p>



<p>___________________________________</p>



<p>Most people give up on stage (4).</p>



<p>After moving through a labor-intensive stage (3), most people feel as if they are finished and are ready for their reward. They don’t realize that after all the hard work there is still time until their goals become realized.</p>



<p>In order for our goals to be realized, our hard work needs to be backed with faith through the (Irrigation Process), then will start growing through (Crop Growth), then finally may become ready to be realized during (Harvesting).</p>



<p>To be truly successful we need to do the work, but also we must be patient and have faith in the process. After all the work is done, it’s now up to mother nature and her perfect timing. We must remain confident, keep up on our schedule, work hard and be patient.</p>



<p>Your harvest season may just be around the corner!</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2020/02/HouseofRoses_trademark_transparent-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-904" width="166" height="178"/></figure></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/patience-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Change</title>
		<link>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/change/</link>
					<comments>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/change/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John Roseli]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 16:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://houseofroses.pnl.nyc/?p=272</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Change, it instills fear into many. Change is about new beginnings and new experiences. Change is the ONLY thing consistent throughout our whole life. So why are many people afraid of it? For one, we are beings of habit. Breaking our habits is tough and [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter"><img src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2018/01/13-Change.jpg" alt="Change" class="wp-image-239"/><figcaption><em>This image was not created by House of Roses. For concerns about this photo please contact: Mr.RosesEmail@gmail.com</em></figcaption></figure></div>



<p></p>



<p>Change, it instills fear into many. Change is about new beginnings and new experiences. Change is the ONLY thing consistent throughout our whole life.</p>



<p>So why are many people afraid of it?</p>



<p>For one, we are beings of habit. Breaking our habits is tough and can make us feel uncomfortable. It’s always easier to take a clear path that has been walked on than to start our own.</p>



<p>Also, just as in nature, we are lazy and always seek to take the path of least resistance.&nbsp;An example of this&nbsp;can be seen in water. Water will rarely flow uphill, but will flow downhill every time with ease. Water flowing downhill is the path of least resistance. In order for water to flow uphill but that would require more effort such as using a pump or being in an area of high pressure.</p>



<p>Change takes work which most people try and avoid.</p>



<p>Another reason people hate change is because as we age we become more resistant towards trying new things. We hit a point where we feel that we can gage what we’re good at and what we’re not good at.</p>



<p>Avoiding change helps reduce the feeling of defeat or embarrassment. People avoid constantly challenge themselves, typically because of past experiences and the fear of looking foolish.</p>



<p>Another major reason people fear change is due to the uncertainty of the future even though it is only temporary uncertainty.&nbsp;Change has many initial questions when introduced such as: Will this be effective? How will others handle it? How will I handle it? Could there be negative impacts?</p>



<p>People always fear what they do not know and the results of change is not always a clear picture.</p>



<p>Change is the ONLY thing consistent in life and the outcomes are unknown. We must all gage the positive and negatives impacts. If the positives outweigh the negatives then it is beneficial. If the negative out weighs the positive, then it may be time to re-organize our plans.</p>



<p>Learn to embrace change and continue growing.</p>



<p>Change is like the movement of water. Running water is always clean and healthy. Stagnant ponds are always filled with disease and bacteria. Humans have the power to pump the pond water out and start it moving again. Don’t be a stagnant pond. Embrace change and get your water moving again.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2020/02/HouseofRoses_trademark_transparent-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-904" width="168" height="180"/></figure></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/change/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sacrifice</title>
		<link>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/sacrifice/</link>
					<comments>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/sacrifice/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John Roseli]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 16:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://houseofroses.pnl.nyc/?p=270</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Anything in life is achievable, if we are willing to put in the work and make sacrifices to achieve our goals. We must first envision, through our imagination, what it is that we want and then think about how we will feel once we’ve achieved [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2018/01/12-The-Scluptor-1024x576.png" alt="Sacrifice" class="wp-image-215"/><figcaption><em>This image was not created by House of Roses. For concerns about this photo please contact: Mr.RosesEmail@gmail.com</em></figcaption></figure>



<p></p>



<p>Anything in life is achievable, if we are willing to put in the work and make sacrifices to achieve our goals. We must first envision, through our imagination, what it is that we want and then think about how we will feel once we’ve achieved our goal.</p>



<p>Once we are certain on what we want, we must then plan the proper steps to take in order to achieve our goals. Our initial plan may not be the perfect route to achieving our goals, it may even fail along the way. But believe me, every time our plan fails we will be one step closer to achieving our goals.</p>



<p>Our failures will show us where our plan is faulted and gives us the opportunity to find a better route to achieve our goals.</p>



<p>Unfortunately, this is easier said then done. Many things seem simple in theory but difficult in practice.</p>



<p>For example: the secret to having a healthy/fit body is no secret at all. In order to have a healthy body that’s fit, you must eat healthy foods and workout. Unfortinatley in society not everyone is healthy and fit, some people don’t care to be while others wish that they were.</p>



<p>For those out there who wish to achieve their goals but for some reason can’t:</p>



<p>It doesn’t matter if you’re struggling to be healthy and fit or struggling for anything else. The only reason that you cannot achieve your goals is because you are not willing to sacrifice what you know you must.</p>



<p>In order to gain anything in this life, something must be sacrificed. Whether it’s our time, the foods we like to eat or events we must miss. Something must be sacrificed if we intend to achieve any of our goals and arrive at something new.</p>



<h4>To become who or what you want to be in life:</h4>



<ul><li>You must first envision the final product</li><li>You must decide on a plan to get there</li><li>You must walk the path of the plan without veering off</li><li>You must suffer when appropriate</li><li>You must learn from mistakes</li><li>You must celebrate your achievements</li></ul>



<p>Discipline and dedication are two key elements needed to transform our goals into plans and our plans into achievements.</p>



<p>We are both the marble and the sculptor. Envision what you want become, then start chipping away.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2020/02/HouseofRoses_trademark_transparent-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-904" width="166" height="178"/></figure></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/sacrifice/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Escape</title>
		<link>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/escape/</link>
					<comments>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/escape/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John Roseli]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 16:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://houseofroses.pnl.nyc/?p=268</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The world we live in can be stressful and energy demanding. It can be overwhelming and complex. At times, everyone needs an escape from the world, an escape from reality, an escape from obligations. This escape is something that all people need. Finding our Escape [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter"><img src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2018/01/10-Escape-225x300.jpg" alt="Escape" class="wp-image-209"/><figcaption><em>This image was not created by House of Roses. For concerns about this photo please contact: Mr.RosesEmail@gmail.com</em></figcaption></figure></div>



<p></p>



<p>The world we live in can be stressful and energy demanding. It can be overwhelming and complex. At times, everyone needs an escape from the world, an escape from reality, an escape from obligations.</p>



<p>This escape is something that all people need. Finding our Escape is critical to our mental health and overall happiness. Life isn’t all about constant movement and work. It is critical to slow down at times and enjoy the little things.</p>



<p>It’s important to clear our mind and give it some time to relax and go about its own natural thought patterns. In a world of constant movement, here are some ways to slow down so that we may enjoy the little things:</p>



<h4>Some ways of escaping from life:</h4>



<ul><li>Spending time with our Family</li><li>Working out</li><li>Listening to Music</li><li>Meditating</li><li>Picking up a Hobby</li><li>Vacationing from Work</li><li>Traveling</li><li>Spending time with friends/meeting new ones</li></ul>



<p>Each escape is a time where personal responsibilities and obligations can be temporarily forgotten. This allows our mind to veer off its training and to go back to its natural thought patterns.</p>



<p>You need to find what works for you, I cannot emphasize enough how important finding an escape is. Without one, we become conditioned to the environments we are forced into. We become people with personalities based off our responsibilities and obligations.</p>



<p>We forget our natural thought patterns and who we actually are as individuals. Remember, all work and no play makes jack a dull boy. Don’t become dull! Find your escape and never loose who you are.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2020/02/HouseofRoses_trademark_transparent-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-904" width="180" height="193"/></figure></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/escape/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Failure</title>
		<link>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/failure/</link>
					<comments>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/failure/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John Roseli]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 16:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://houseofroses.pnl.nyc/?p=266</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Any successful person who claims they never failed is a liar. Failure is essential to success. It’s unavoidable but luckily it’s the ultimate teacher. If understood correctly, it is the most important factor that makes ordinary people extraordinary. Failure is like electricity. If controlled properly [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="300" height="169" src="/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/kkkkkkk.jpg" alt="Failure" class="wp-image-567"/><figcaption><em>This image was not created by House of Roses. For concerns about this photo please contact: Mr.RosesEmail@gmail.com</em></figcaption></figure></div>



<p></p>



<p>Any successful person who claims they never failed is a liar. Failure is essential to success. It’s unavoidable but luckily it’s the ultimate teacher. If understood correctly, it is the most important factor that makes ordinary people extraordinary.</p>



<p>Failure is like electricity. If controlled properly it can do amazing things and in some instanced it helps bring people back to life (defibrillator). Also, if not controlled properly it can cause great damage and potentially kill (lightning).</p>



<p>The two different ways of looking at failure:</p>



<p><strong>Pessimistic views</strong>&nbsp;– When faced with a failure the pessimistic thinkers begin by feeling down on themselves. Most believe it is a sign that they will never be good enough to achieve their goals. It kills self-confidence and spirit. Failure makes most people feel embarrassed and self-conscious. It can diminish all will power to prevail and succeed. This way of thinking can kill all movement towards one’s goals.</p>



<p><strong>Optimistic views:</strong>&nbsp;– When faced with failure the optimistic response is taken quite differently from the pessimistic. While the pessimistic sulks, the optimistic analyzes their failure. The optimist tries to learn from their failure. They break down every step and find where the fault in their plan lies. They believe that the war is not over and in every lost battle there is a lesson to be learnt that will lead to victory in the end.</p>



<p>Failure is a teacher who shows us the faults in our plan and makes sure we don’t forget them.</p>



<p>In this life, we must deal with failure often. We are all imperfect humans and are bound to fail at times. If we fail at something, that means we’re making an attempt towards a new goal but don’t quite have the plan right yet. Most people are so scared to fail that they stop attempting new things and stop re-adjusting their plans.</p>



<p>When humans stop attempting new things, we stop growing. We need to change our perspective on failure and look at it as lesson we are learning on our path to success. When striving to accomplishing our goals and become successful, failure is almost inevitable.</p>



<p>Learn from your mistakes and come back stronger!</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2020/02/HouseofRoses_trademark_transparent-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-904" width="182" height="195"/></figure></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/failure/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Organization</title>
		<link>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/organization/</link>
					<comments>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/organization/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John Roseli]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 16:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://houseofroses.pnl.nyc/?p=264</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In order to be successful, there are many different things that go into the magical formula that changes dreams into reality. One of the key elements is organizational skills. Not only in organization of our work, but also in organization of our daily life and [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2017/12/9-Organization-300x169.jpg" alt="Organization" class="wp-image-186" width="300" height="169"/><figcaption><em>This image was not created by House of Roses. For concerns about this photo please contact: Mr.RosesEmail@gmail.com</em></figcaption></figure></div>



<p></p>



<p>In order to be successful, there are many different things that go into the magical formula that changes dreams into reality. One of the key elements is organizational skills. Not only in organization of our work, but also in organization of our daily life and mind.</p>



<p>By this I mean organization of our desk at work, our home, our room, our extracurricular activities, our bills, our priorities, our emotions and so on. Organization multiplies our spirit, boosts energy levels and increases efficiency.</p>



<p>Throughout the day people subconsciously waste their energy, some examples could be:</p>



<ol><li>Deciding on what clothing to wear during the day.</li><li>Deciding on what food to eat during the day.</li><li>Deciding on what activities to do during the day.</li><li>Looking for personal/work items around the house/office.</li><li>Deciding on when to workout or exercise.</li><li>Deciding on when to do one’s laundry.</li><li>Deciding on when to clean one’s house.</li><li>Deciding when to clean and re-organize ones workplace.</li></ol>



<p>The list could go on forever. The point to be understood is that these small decisions take different amounts of mental energies for each person to decide upon and when added together could be a substantial amount of energy being used.</p>



<p>In order to conserve energy, many random tasks like the ones mentioned above could be organized into a set pattern that will eventually become a habit. Habits form through repetition and create automatic responses resulting in low energy usage.</p>



<h4>Benefits of organization</h4>



<p>As a person becomes better at planning their personal/business lives, more habits will form and most of life’s simple tasks will become automatic resulting in more available energy.</p>



<p>The great thing with habits is that once they become automatic, they require much smaller amounts of energy. The key to developing these habits is to first become organized and second to be disciplines and stick to the schedule. Some examples of basic decision we must make everyday that we can program to become automatic:</p>



<ol><li>I will wear (x) sets of clothing in a cycle during the weeks at work.</li><li>I will pre-plan my meals for the week and stay consistent.</li><li>I will spend time with friends on these days (x) and work on my goals on these days (x).</li><li>I will organize my house/office like this (x).</li><li>I will work out on these days (x).</li><li>I will do laundry every (x).</li><li>I will clean my house every (x).</li><li>I will organize my desk in (x) way.</li><li>I will clean up my desks workplace every (x).</li></ol>



<p>These small organizational habits that can be formed will save great amount of energy and allow for greater heights of achievement to be reached in other areas.</p>



<p>“A well-organized desk indicates a well-organized brain, as there is a close relationship between one’s mental attitude and one’s physical environment. “ –Napoleon Hill</p>



<p>Stay organized and try to turn basic tasks into habits. This is a great principle that will ensure higher mental energy levels.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2020/02/HouseofRoses_trademark_transparent-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-904" width="178" height="190"/></figure></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/organization/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pressure</title>
		<link>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/pressure/</link>
					<comments>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/pressure/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John Roseli]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 16:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://houseofroses.pnl.nyc/?p=262</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Pressure. Is it worth it? Is it worth it to you? If not, then what is it that you should do? Do you have a choice? Is there an angle you can see? Where you’re at now, is it what’s meant to be? Pressure can [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter"><img src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2017/12/8-Pressure-300x199.jpg" alt="Pressure" class="wp-image-181"/><figcaption><em>This image was not created by House of Roses. For concerns about this photo please contact: Mr.RosesEmail@gmail.com</em></figcaption></figure></div>



<p></p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Pressure.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Is it worth it?</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Is it worth it to you?</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">If not,</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">then what is it that you should do?</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Do you have a choice?</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Is there an angle you can see?</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Where you’re at now,</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">is it what’s meant to be?</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Pressure can be good,</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">it can also be bad.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">You must resist from getting mad.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">If the passion is there then the pressure is good.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">If not, then the pressure can destroy you, understood?</p>



<p class="has-text-align-right">By: Mr. Roses</p>



<p></p>



<p>Pressure is typical when competing in life’s game of survival. Everyone must decide on what that means for them. Everyone must decide on two things:</p>



<ul><li>How they will eat/drink.</li><li>Where they will find shelter.</li></ul>



<p>Of course on a more grander scale there are many other concerns such as areas to live, places to work, the safety of your family and so on. But to the three most basic needs for humans, we need food, water and shelter. Even just securing these three basic needs could put a great amount pressure on a person.</p>



<p>Everyone needs to decide on what type of lifestyle is suitable for them. Once decided on, they need to chase and pursue that lifestyle. Any type of lifestyle will take some effort/sacrifice to achieve/maintain and will put some level of pressure on that individual. To live a happy life everyone needs to take the following steps and decide what type of pressures they wish to endure:</p>



<ol><li>Decide on what type of lifestyle you want to live.</li><li>Develop a plan on how you wish to achieve that lifestyle.</li><li>Cross analyze your lifestyle and plan in the following ways:</li></ol>



<p></p>



<ul><li>Is this truly the lifestyle that you want to live?</li><li>Is your plan to achieve this lifestyle a practical plan?</li><li>Have you critically looked at your plan from every angle and calculated the points where you may fail?</li><li>Have you developed a plan on what you will do if your plan doesn’t go accordingly?</li><li>Is the lifestyle you want to live worth the pressures that you will face down the road and are you ready to face and conquer those pressures?</li></ul>



<p>Remember, not all pressure is bad. Pressure directed towards the right goals can be a great moving force for achievement. Decide on what type of pressures are beneficial to your chosen quality of life and then eliminate all negative pressures.</p>



<p>When striving for your goals, you may fail and most likely will at one point or another. However, failure is only failure when you choose to give up. If you look at failure as lessons highlighting where your plan was flawed, then you may reach your goals quicker than expected.</p>



<p>Final thoughts: Diamonds are made under extreme pressure. Decide on your goal, work hard and never give up. Become a diamond and face the pressures of your chosen lifestyle.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2020/02/HouseofRoses_trademark_transparent-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-904" width="177" height="189"/></figure></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/pressure/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Courage</title>
		<link>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/courage/</link>
					<comments>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/courage/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John Roseli]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 16:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://houseofroses.pnl.nyc/?p=260</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What is to come? What is to be? I’m scared of what will happen, that’s between you and me. I must continue on, even though I don’t know. The challenges I’ll face that I must undergo. The reason behind my journey is important indeed. Regardless [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter"><img src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2017/12/7-Courage-300x300.png" alt="" class="wp-image-175"/><figcaption><em>This image was not created by House of Roses. For concerns about this photo please contact: Mr.RosesEmail@gmail.com</em></figcaption></figure></div>



<p></p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">What is to come?</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">What is to be?</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">I’m scared of what will happen,</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">that’s between you and me.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">I must continue on,</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">even though I don’t know.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">The challenges I’ll face that I must undergo.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">The reason behind my journey is important indeed.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Regardless of the challenges, I’m sure to succeed.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-right">By: Mr. Roses</p>



<p></p>



<p>Throughout life there will be many uncertainties. We as humans can never know the outcome of what will happen in the future. All that we can do is speculate, gather facts and make predictions. We must use these predictions to take educated guesses in order to continue progression in any given work, project or personal task.</p>



<p>Progressing based off prediction and educated guesses isn’t always the easiest thing to do. It takes a certain amount of courage to continue moving forward over uncertain grounds due to the potential of failure.</p>



<p>Courage is a vital force that drives success through uncertain times. To accomplish anything great you need courage. In order to be courageous, you must do the following:</p>



<p>– Believe in yourself, whether it be something regarding your work, your own project or a personal task in life.</p>



<p>– Analyze all the potential benefits of preceding over these uncertain grounds.</p>



<p>– Analyze all the potential failures of preceding over these uncertain grounds.</p>



<p>– Decide upon the importance of this task and decide if the benefits outweigh the consequences of failure.</p>



<p>Deciding to precede over uncertain grounds is a sign of courage, but only if the above steps have been taken. Anyone can precede forward over uncertain grounds with ignorance. It takes true courage to proceed through uncertain grounds with full awareness of the potential failures.</p>



<p>Analyze these failures, decide if the benefits are worth the risk and if they are, move forward with courage!</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2020/02/HouseofRoses_trademark_transparent-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-904" width="175" height="187"/></figure></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/courage/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mindset vs. Fear</title>
		<link>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/mindset-vs-fear/</link>
					<comments>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/mindset-vs-fear/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John Roseli]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 16:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://houseofroses.pnl.nyc/?p=258</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It’s true, typically the things that change us and help us grow are the ones that scare us the most. Usually the things that scare us the most are the things that we don’t think we can accomplish. The fear of failure is actually what [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2017/12/6-Mindset-Vs-Fear-1024x576.png" alt="Mindset Vs Fear" class="wp-image-160" width="381" height="214"/><figcaption><em>This image was not created by House of Roses. For concerns about this photo please contact: Mr.RosesEmail@gmail.com</em></figcaption></figure></div>



<p></p>



<p>It’s true, typically the things that change us and help us grow are the ones that scare us the most. Usually the things that scare us the most are the things that we don’t think we can accomplish. The fear of failure is actually what scares us.</p>



<p>What’s important to understand is that this fear of failure is a self-inflicted false reality. It’s a mindset that holds you captive from doing what you believe in your heart you should do.</p>



<h4>A few examples:</h4>



<p><strong>1.)</strong>&nbsp;Take a child who is scared to go into their room alone at night. The child fears that there are monsters in the room and is too scared to go into the dark room alone. This fear of the monsters is just a mindset that blocks the child from going into their room alone late at night.</p>



<p>Adults know monsters don’t exist but the child doesn’t. Until the child matures and gets over the fear of monsters, this fear mindset that there are monsters in the room will have some control over the child’s actions. Thus blocking the child from going into the room alone at night due to a false reality.</p>



<p><strong>2.)</strong>&nbsp;Take a guy scared to talk to a girl. He fears what she will say or maybe even what he will say. So that fear can potentially stop him from taking action and talking to the girl he admires.</p>



<p>Until he can finally over come this mindset and take a chance even though it scares him, he will never grow, he will never develop the courage to talk to girls and never truly know what the outcome of his efforts could be.</p>



<p><strong>3.)</strong>&nbsp;Now say we have a person who wants to take a chance with a new work decision. Maybe if they fail, they will be left with nothing. Is it worth the risk? That’s up to them, only they could decide.</p>



<p>They need think about the worst possible situation they could get themselves into. Set a plan on what they would do if the worst happened. If they feel comfortable with their plan and truly believe in their decision, then they can over come their fear and free themselves from the fear mindset.</p>



<p>Mindsets can entrap us. Identify which ones are holding you back, then make an educated leap of faith and break the chains.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2020/02/HouseofRoses_trademark_transparent-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-904" width="166" height="178"/></figure></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/mindset-vs-fear/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stressed</title>
		<link>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/stressed/</link>
					<comments>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/stressed/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John Roseli]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 16:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://houseofroses.pnl.nyc/?p=256</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Stressed, Stressed. Life moves along. Stressed, Stressed. You must be strong. Stressed, Stressed. Not the only one. Stressed, Stressed. Rise like the sun. By: Mr. Roses In today’s day in age, stress is normal. Speaking from someone who works in New York City, the city [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter"><img src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2017/12/5-Stresed-Post.jpg" alt="Stressed" class="wp-image-154"/><figcaption><em>This image was not created by House of Roses. For concerns about this photo please contact: Mr.RosesEmail@gmail.com</em></figcaption></figure></div>



<p></p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Stressed, Stressed.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Life moves along.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Stressed, Stressed.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">You must be strong.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Stressed, Stressed.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Not the only one.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Stressed, Stressed.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Rise like the sun.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-right">By: Mr. Roses</p>



<p></p>



<p>In today’s day in age, stress is normal. Speaking from someone who works in New York City, the city that never sleeps, it’s action 24/7. Sometimes work could become so overwhelming that our life begins to revolve around it.</p>



<p>In a very competitive work economy, we must be aggressive in completing our tasks or risk getting replaced. This constant work flow and competitive environment breaths stress.</p>



<p>We may start to find ourselves moving constantly at 100 mph trying to achieve our tasks at work and sometimes this’s required.</p>



<p>Due to the consistency of the work load and the need to be moving fast at all times, we tend to forget how to slow down outside of work. Life starts to move more rapidly and happiness starts to decline.</p>



<p>We become entrapped in the work world stress. Then during any free time where we have the opportunity to try and free ourself from these burdens, all we want to do is crash and relax at 0mph.</p>



<h4>How to decompress</h4>



<p>It is critical to find out how to slow down our pace in life. Sometimes at work we need to be aggressive and work at 100 mph, but not all of life is like that. Life is something we want to try and cruise at a nice 50 mph.</p>



<p>We all need to break this 0 mph or 100 mph lifestyle and learn how to pump the breaks. As the great Ferris Bueller stated “Life moves pretty fast. If you don’t stop and look around once in a while, you could miss it.”</p>



<p>The stresses you are facing now are preparing you for something great in the future. Study your habits and find the things that are causing most of your stress. Try and implement alternative habits that can reduce your stress.</p>



<p>Try things like exercising, meditating or spending time with friends and family. If all fails, remember that diamonds are made under great pressure. Keep in mind life moves from 0 to 100 mph very quickly and remember the power you have to make life what you want it to be.</p>



<p>Start with a goal, develop a plan and work until you achieve your goal!</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://houseofroses.org/wp-content/uploads/sites/14/2020/02/HouseofRoses_trademark_transparent-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-904" width="183" height="196"/></figure></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/HouseOfRoses-Static/static/2020/07/10/stressed/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
